http://www.diversifiedcu.org/about-us/privacy-notice/

Privacy NoticeFACTSWHAT DOES DIVERSIFIED CREDIT UNION (DCU) DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and payment historyCredit history and credit scoreWhen you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons DCU chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes DCU share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to youNoWe don’t shareFor joint marketing with other financial companiesNoWe don’t shareFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiencesN/AN/AFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthinessN/AN/AFor affiliates to market to youN/AN/AFor nonaffiliates to market to youN/AN/AQuestions?Call 612.321.5300What We DoHow does DCU protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does DCU collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when you:open an account or deposit moneypay your bills or apply for a loanuse your credit card or debit cardWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus or other companies.Why can’t I limit all my sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit only:sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for non-affiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.DefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.NonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Joint MarketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. Website Privacy PolicyDiversified Credit Union uses Google Analytics to track visitor statistics on diversifiedcu.org. Google Analytics records:What website you came from to get hereHow long you stayWhat kind of computer you’re usingAnd quite a bit moreOccasionally, we review these statistics to learn more about the number of visitors this site receives and browsers being used. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. All activity falls within the bounds of the Google Analytics Terms of Service.Want to opt out of tracking? You can opt out of Google’s advertising tracking cookie or use a browser plugin to opt out of all Google Analytics tracking software.DisclaimerThis Website is provided by Diversified Credit Union to furnish our members with information about credit union programs and services. All information presented is believed to be accurate, however, accuracy cannot be guaranteed. This Website is not intended to render accounting, tax, legal, or other professional advice or services.
Diversified Credit UnionPhone: 800-333-7757 toll-free   |   Linden CenterPoint Office   |   Waseca Branch
